const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'What Thee Avalanche rescue tools should you have on your person at all times in the backcountry?',
        answers: [
            'Water, food, shelter',
            'Helmet, airbag, avalung',
            'Beacon, shovel, probe',
            'Bacon, eggs, potatos'],
        correctAnswer: 'beacon, shovel, probe'
    },
    {
        question: 'At about what slope steepness do avalanches become a hazard?',
        answers: [
            '15-20 degrees',
            '25-30 degrees',
            '25-30 degrees',
            '45-50 degrees'],
        correctAnswer: '25-30 degrees'
    },
    {
        question: 'How does the popular beacon use saying go?',
        answers: [
            '"On at the car, off at the Bar"',
            '"On at the top, off at the bottom"',
            '"On when it\'s steep, off when it\'s not"',
            '"On when you need it, off when you don\'t"'],
        correctAnswer: '"On at the car, off at the Bar"'
    },
    {
        question: 'In a group of riders/ skiers, how should downhill travel be handled \
        in avalanche territory?',
        answers: [
            'PARTY SKI!!!',
            'Drop one at a time, all others keeping eyes on the rider',
            'Leeap frog every 500',
            'Drop one at a time, seperated by 2 mins'],
        correctAnswer: 'Drop one at a time, all others keeping eyes on the rider'
    },
    {
        question: 'If your partner triggers an avalanche, what do you do first?',
        answers: [
            'Call 911',
            'Bomb the hill after them',
            'Alert everyone of an avalanche and switch all beacons to search mode',
            'Give up immediately'],
        correctAnswer: 'Alert everyone of an avalanche and switch all beacons to search mode'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where do you start your beacon search?',
        answers: [
            'Where you are standing',
            'At the avalanche crown',
            'At the last seen point of those cought',
            'At the bottom'],
        correctAnswer: 'At the last seen point of those cought'
    },
    {
        question: 'What do you do after getting as close as you can with a beacon?',
        answers: [
            'Dig',
            'Call search and rescue',
            'Probe until you find the buried person',
            'Take a break, you found them'],
        correctAnswer: 'Probe until you find the buried person'
    },
    {
        question: 'When a victem becomes completely burried, how much time do you have \
        to rescue them before likely asphixiation?',
        answers: [
            '5 minutes',
            '15 minutes',
            '45 minutes',
            '1 hour'],
        correctAnswer: '15 minutes'
    },
    {
        question: 'When digging someone out, where do you srart?',
        answers: [
            'At the probe, straight down',
            '3 feet left or right of the probe',
            'About 100cm down hill from the probe',
            'Up hill from the probe'],
        correctAnswer: 'about 100cm down hill from the probe'
    },
    {
        question: 'Why is it important to skilled partners you trust when going into\
        the backcountry?',
        answers: [
            'If an avalanche occurs, they are your means of rescue',
            'Skilled partners help make informed decisions',
            'Trust and mutual respect helps with communication',
            'All of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'All of the above'
    }];     
